thegiantsofmarketing.com 2010-11-29

# The Giants Of Marketing

**Privacy Policy**

The Giants of Marketing privacy policy was last updated 22nd May 2009.

* * *

**Privacy Policy**

By accessing or using the The Giants of Marketing web site, you agree to the terms of the The Giants of Marketing Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. The Giants of Marketing reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Privacy Policy at the time of such use.

**Collection of personal information**  
When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering products, downloading software, or entering contests, The Giants of Marketing may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, The Giants of Marketing may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

In the process of administering our site, we maintain and track usage through Web server logs. Web server logs provide such information as what types of browsers are accessing our site, what pages receive high traffic, and the times of day our servers experience significant load. We use this information to improve the content and navigation features of our site. It is not used to personally identify you.

**How your personal information is used**  
The Giants of Marketing collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. The information that you provide is also used as part of our effort to keep you informed about special offers and other products and services of The Giants of Marketing and selected third parties.

Please note, when you sign-up for service with a The Giants of Marketing branded company (The Giants of Marketing, JVA Net) you are opted in to our regular newsletter and customer update email notifications which is sent to customers on a regular basis. You can opt-out of the newsletter at anytime by clicking on the “opt-out” link that is sent with every email we send.

**How we share your personal information**  
We will not sell, rent or lease to others telephone numbers or e-mail addresses. We will share the personal data you provide only with other The Giants of Marketing entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above, except as provided below (see Consent).

**Consent**  
The Giants of Marketing will use and share the personally identifiable information you provided to us in ways related to those described above. We reserve the right to disclose any and all pertinent customer information to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.

**Reprinting personal information**  
Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board or chat room, is available to all persons accessing that site.

**Privacy related concerns**  
Should you have questions or concerns relating to this Privacy Statement or compliance with it, please send e-mail to: info@The Giants of Marketing.com
